searchalgo.com 2019-07-15

# searchalgo.com Privacy

## Privacy Policy

This privacy statement describes how searchalgo.com collects and uses the Personal Information you provide on our Web site: searchalgo.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact us at [admin@searchalgo.com](mailto:admin@searchalgo.com).

### Collection and Use of Information

searchalgo.com does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information").

searchalgo.com may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at searchalgo.com's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. searchalgo.com's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information. 

searchalgo.com may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. searchalgo.com collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. searchalgo.com will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

### Sharing and Disclosure of Information

searchalgo.com does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. searchalgo.com may disclose information about its users if searchalgo.com believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on searchalgo.com; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of searchalgo.com (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of searchalgo.com services or members of the public.

### Security

searchalgo.com takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although searchalgo.com cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, searchalgo.com has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of searchalgo.com. If you submit Personal Information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

### Business Transitions

In the event that searchalgo.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. searchalgo.com will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information searchalgo.com may have prior to such transfer.

### Changes to Policy

From time to time, searchalgo.com may revise this Policy. searchalgo.com will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information searchalgo.com collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. 

### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

**searchalgo.com**  
Email: admin@searchalgo.com  

© 2019 searchalgo.com.
